(All characters and organisations in this drama are fictional.)
(Filming with minors followed broadcast guidelines,)
(and generative AI was used in select scenes.)
Hold on.
Look there.
(1 Year Later)
I was so happy.
Gyu Rim is in a relationship.
Mu Jin.
- I missed you. - Me too.
Have you been waiting long?
We worry that Mu Jin...
- What did you put on me? - will take Gyu Rim away from us...
- No. - You put something on me, right?
- I didn't. - What's this? You did it again.
- No. - You put this on me, right?
Don't take it off.
What is this?
- There's one more. - There's more?
- Yes. - Where is it?
(Mu Jin's)
Hi.
Have you been studying hard?
- Aren't you hungry? - This is what Mu Jin told us.
Gyu Rim.
- Gyu Min. - Oh, you're here?
- Gyu Rim. - Hey.
Were you all eating?
- Honey, what do you want to eat? - I'll have black bean noodles too.
One more order of black bean noodles, please.
- Gyu Seo, I mixed it all for you. - Is it good?
Gyu Seo. Gyu Min.
"I'm not taking your sister Gyu Rim away from you."
"I'm coming to you to be a big brother to Gyu Seo...
- "and a big brother to Gyu Min." - It's okay.
You're so cute.
- What should we eat next time? - We...
Decided to trust what Mu Jin said.
Father.
Hello, sir.
And who...
Might this be?
My name is Kim Mu Jin.
He's Gyu Rim's boyfriend.
Boyfriend?
Gyu Rim, you...
Are dating someone?
- You two go inside and wash up. - Okay.
- Goodbye. - Okay.
- Thank you for the meal. - Sure. Let's eat again.
Let's go again next time.
Father.
He's very handsome.
My Gyu Rim...
Really landed a catch.
Thank you.
If you had such a wonderful boyfriend,
You should have introduced him to me first.
So, how long have you two been seeing each other?
It's been about one year now.
I'm sorry for not introducing myself sooner.
- A year? - Yes.
If it's already been a year, my goodness.
Then you must be thinking about marriage, right?
- Oh, it's not like that. - Yes, it is.
- Mu Jin. - If you'll give us your permission,
I'd like to marry Gyu Rim.
I like how straightforward you are, my Son-in-law Kim.
Well, since we're on the topic,
Let's just set a date before the end of the year.
That sounds good to me.
It's not like that. Not yet, Father.
We still need to work more, earn more money...
Earn money? Why? Our Son-in-law Kim is wealthy.
He's not from a wealthy family.
He's just a part-timer who works where I do.
Then why are you working part-time wearing a watch...
Worth hundreds of thousands of dollars?
- What? - Oh, the heirs hiding identity...
For management training or something like that?
I told you, it's not like that.
Besides, who has a watch worth hundreds of thousands of dollars?
Did you tell my Gyu Rim you were poor?
What, because you were afraid my Gyu Rim...
Would feel insecure and get intimidated?
Father, you're misunderstanding.
My goodness, this guy is so considerate.
Well, the thing is...
I told you, it's not like that. Really.
It's a knockoff.
- A knockoff? - Yes.
It's a knockoff from Namdaemun Market.
Then...
Your belt and shoes...
Are they all knockoffs, then?
Yes.
And you're not from a wealthy family?
No.
And you're not rich?
He's just like me, working hard...
To live an honest life. That's Mu Jin.
Why would you date a guy like this?
So the two of you can starve together?
- Father! - Oh, sure.
I should've known about your taste in men.
Break up with him. Right now, while I'm asking nicely.
- Father. - "Hardworking." Give me a break.
I know his type, okay? A young punk with nothing to his name...
Is already obsessed with luxury brands.
I mean, if you can't afford them, then...
You should just give them up and learn to live within your means.
But looking at this earlier,
Even if it's a knockoff,
It looks like a top-quality replica.
These knockoff watches still sell for a lot of money.
It wasn't that expensive...
Who are you trying to fool...
With a high-end knockoff like this?
- Who are you trying to trick? - Father.
It's a misunderstanding.
I really only care about Gyu Rim.
Enough.
Go. Get lost. Get away from my daughter...
Right now. Got it?
Father, why are you doing this? Really.
Don't you see it? After looking at me?
He's just like I was when I was young.
Exactly like me.
Hey, because she chose the wrong guy,
Her life was ruined.
Haven't you learned from what happened to your mom?
Mu Jin is different.
At least he's not like you, deceiving Mom...
And lying all the time.
You, get over here.
Stop hiding behind a woman like a coward.
Don't just stand there. Get over here.
Guys like this need a lesson...
So they don't come sniffing around again.
You're going to get a beating today. Got it?
Come here. Hey.
- Father. - Hey.
Don't you dare lay a finger on Mu Jin.
I don't care if you're my father. I won't let it slide. I mean it.
Han Gyu Rim, move.
Are you going to move?
Darn it. You, get over here, you punk.
- Hey. - Mu Jin, just go. I'll call you.
Hey, get over here.
- Mu Jin, just go. Go. - I'll see you next time, sir.
- Where do you think you're going? - Father, stop it. Honestly.
- Hey. - I can't believe this.
- Get inside. You, get inside. - Father, honestly.
Whose side are you on already?
You said you wouldn't just stand by. What are you going to do about it?
Are you going to hit me? Unbelievable.
Hey, Han Gyu Young, Han Gyu Oh.
Your innocent and naive older sister...
While she was dating that mindless punk,
Why didn't you stop her?
- Let's talk about this. - You have to let go of me, Father.
Gosh, my shoulder.
Hey, Han Gyu Young.
You're supposed to be a good judge of men. What did you do?
And what did you do, Father?
If you disapproved so much, you should've...
Come home and stopped her yourself.
She was crazy in love. How was I supposed to stop her?
Han Gyu Young.
Father, please stop.
I told you I was against it from the start.
Kicking people out is your specialty, isn't it, Father?
You kicked out Mom too.
So I guess it's up to you to do whatever it takes...
To stop Han Gyu Rim, right?
You...
Han Gyu Oh, what about you, you punk?
I was cheering for her.
I was hoping things would go well with her boyfriend...
So she could get out of this miserable house.
I was rooting for her like crazy.
I can't believe this kid.
Go for it, Han Gyu Rim. I'm totally rooting for you.
No matter who you date,
At least they'll be better than Father, right?
- Why you little... - What about us?
Why aren't you asking us?
- I approve. - I'm neutral for now.
- Then why did you eat the noodles? - Hey.
Elementary schoolers don't get a say. Got it?
You two, go to your room. Now. Go on, hurry.
Those two are just the same.
Anyway, I'm...
Until you tell me you won't see that punk anymore,
I'm going on a hunger strike.
If you want to save your father, break up with him.
If you want to kill your father, then keep seeing that guy.
Got it? Darn it.
Should I have just told him it was real?
Mu Jin is different.
At least he's not like you, deceiving Mom...
And lying all the time.
No.
What should I do?
(I'll Protect My Daughter! Hunger Strike: Day One)
I'll protect my daughter. Hunger strike, day one.
- Hello. - Hi.
- Mu Jin. - You're just getting here?
Long day?
What are you doing here at this hour?
I figured I could see you if I came around this time.
- Can you spare a moment? - Now?
Yes, now. For about...
Three hours, give or take?
Three hours?
Well, making dinner for the kids and sending them to school...
Gyu Young or Gyu Oh can do that, can't they?
What is it? Is it urgent?
Yes. It's urgent.
Is it important?
Yes. It's important.
I wonder if any stores are open at this hour.
What's with this fancy car?
It doesn't look like it's Jung Woo's.
Where are we going?
To see my father.
What?
I met your father yesterday.
I want to introduce you to my father.
Right now? So suddenly? So out of the blue?
Did I prepare before meeting your father?
But still.
Looking like this?
I'm a total mess right now.
I haven't washed my hair or my face,
And I'm wearing a tracksuit.
You're pretty even without washing your face,
And you look beautiful just as you are.
But just in case, I brought you some clothes.
Shoes too.
Want to change at a rest stop?
- You even brought clothes? - Yes. I wanted...
To introduce you to my father as soon as possible.
Still, this isn't right.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry, but...
Please just do as I ask this one time, Gyu Rim.
(Gohyang Rest Stop)
You look beautiful.
It really suits you.
Since you were so insistent, Mu Jin, I'm doing as you asked for now,
But I have no idea what this is all about.
Thank you.
Thank you so much, Gyu Rim.
Let's go.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
My name is Han Gyu Rim.
If I had known I would be meeting you,
I would have at least brought some flowers.
I apologise.
This is my girlfriend, Father.
She's the woman I love more than anything.
I'm planning on marrying her someday.
But I've been lying to Gyu Rim.
I never meant to deceive her for this long.
I tried to tell her so many times,
But I was afraid she'd get scared and run away.
Oh my goodness, sir.
You should have told us you were coming.
Sir, we're in the middle of something important...
Pardon?
Oh, yes. Of course. I'll just wait downstairs, then.
Please let me know if you need anything.
- Okay. - Yes, sir.
That watch from yesterday...
It wasn't a fake, was it?
That incredibly expensive car we came in,
That's your car, isn't it, Mu Jin?
And this outfit I'm wearing is super expensive too, right?
Mu Jin.
You're not just some poor part-timer, are you?
Was my father right about you?
Were you learning how to manage the restaurant?
Yes.
I tried to tell you so many times...
But I was afraid you'd feel overwhelmed.
I was afraid you'd be angry that I lied to you.
So...
I was afraid you'd be disappointed and leave me.
I couldn't work up the courage.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Gyu Rim.
I'm so sorry for lying to you.
Gyu Rim.
Please say something.
Let me think about it.
- Gyu Rim. - I need to think about it!
What am I supposed to do in this situation?
My boyfriend is a rich heir.
I've hit the jackpot.
Should I be happy about this?
Should I be furious with myself...
For being fooled like an idiot?
Should I be embarrassed for comforting...
A rich heir doing management training,
Acting all high and mighty?
Or should I decide this isn't right?
That he's out of my league?
And that I should end things with a man like Kim Mu Jin?
I need some time to think.
Ma'am, we're here.
- Ma'am. - Yes?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Hey, Gyu Rim.
Is something wrong?
No.
Did Gyu Min and Gyu Seo go to school?
Gyu Seo forgot her bag, so I just dropped it off for her.
- Thanks. Let's go inside. - About what I said yesterday...
I meant it.
I hope you get married soon...
So you can fly away from this miserable home.
Gyu Min said he's a good guy, right?
Don't worry about Father. Just do what you want.
My mouth is watering.
Didn't you say you were on a hunger strike?
At my age, a hunger strike could kill me.
How can you oppose Gyu Rim with an attitude like that?
It's fine. I'm a good actor. Watch.
Look...
I look like nothing but skin and bones, right?
No.
Hey, hey, just say you ate this.
(I'll Protect My Daughter! Hunger Strike: Day One)
Darn it.
What's all that noise?
While your father is starving to death,
You abandon your family...
To go gallivanting around?
Father hasn't had even one sip of water since yesterday.
If something happens to him, what are you going to do?
Are you in your right mind, stuffing your face with bibimbap...
Before our dad, on a hunger strike?
I was just eating the kids' leftovers...
- so they wouldn't go to waste. - That's nonsense.
Since when do you eat the kids' leftovers?
Go ahead and eat, Father.
What?
What's that...
What are you talking about?
Does this mean you're not going to see...
That guy anymore?
She's telling you to go ahead and eat...
Because she knows you were eating.
I told you I was eating that.
Starting tomorrow, to stop you seeing that guy,
I'm going to follow you everywhere. So you'd better watch out.
Hey.
Isn't it so savoury?
No.
Mu Jin.
Kim Mu Jin. Did you sprain your ankle?
Did a snake bite you? Why can't you suddenly walk?
I don't know.
I just can't walk.
You're not injured or anything. You're just saying you can't walk?
Gosh, you scared me.
Hey.
- Let's try walking. - I told Han Gyu Rim everything.
I brought her to my father...
And told her everything.
That I'm not just a part-time worker.
That I'd been deceiving her this whole time.
And that's why you can't walk?
I should have just told her.
I should have told her everything from the beginning.
So what did she say?
I don't know.
She seemed really mad.
She seemed so angry...
That I couldn't even stop her.
Of course she's mad.
I'd be furious if I were her.
"Was this jerk testing me this whole time?"
"Or..."
"was he afraid that if I knew he was a rich heir,"
"I would cling to him and never let go?"
- Darn it. - Is that why you lied for a year?
Hey. You know that's not it.
You know better than anyone that's not it.
From Gyu Rim's point of view, that's what she might think.
The only thing she has is her pride,
And you're the one who hurt it.
Didn't you know this would happen once you revealed everything?
That's why you kept worrying about it.
If it were me,
I would be clapping like a seal.
Oh my gosh, what is happening. This is amazing.
Mu Jin, I'll love you even more from now on.
I would have accepted it just like that.
If she cursed at me, I was ready to take it all,
And if she hit me, I was ready to take that too...
Darn it.
What do I do, Jung Woo? I'm so scared.
What if she just suddenly...
Says she wants to break up...
What will I do if she leaves me?
What do I do if she just runs away from me?
You'll break up. You won't break up.
You'll break up.
You won't break up.
What does it say?
- You won't break up. - We won't break up?
- You'll break up. - Come on. Do it properly.
- Hold on, hold on. - There's another one.
- Okay, let's go. We can do this. - Okay.
- You'll break up. - You'll break up.
You won't break up.
You won't break up. You'll break up. You won't break up.
- You'll break up. - Should've with "You'll break up".
- Gosh, honestly. - Just do it one more time.
This is my fifth cup of coffee.
Seo Hyun, this is your chance.
What are you talking about?
Anyway, you said you had some big, good news.
What is it?
It's Mu Jin.
He and Gyu Rim might break up.
Want me to get you some water?
For real?
- Why all of a sudden? - Mu Jin spilled the beans...
That he's actually...
- a rich heir. - And?
And Han Gyu Rim said she wants to break up?
We don't know yet.
She was so shocked, she didn't say a word...
And just left.
Left and went where?
Where were they for him to tell her?
At Mu Jin's father's grave. He told her there.
He introduced Gyu Rim to his father too.
He took her all the way to his father's grave?
Yes.
And what were you doing?
While Kim Mu Jin and Han Gyu Rim were getting so serious,
Why didn't you do anything to stop them?
You said you were confident you could make her fall for you.
Well, about that...
Turns out Gyu Rim is fiercely loyal, just like someone I know.
Admirably so.
Darn it, if only you were a little more handsome...
Or a little uglier.
And what about you?
Hey, what have you been doing this whole time...
Instead of trying to win over Kim Mu Jin?
He only has eyes for Han Gyu Rim. What was I supposed to do?
Oh, look at Ms. Smarty-pants.
You don't even know how to use your good looks.
My goodness.
Talk about the pot calling the kettle black.
Unbelievable.
Excuse me, could you get up?
Stop pretending to be asleep.
Can't you please just give up your seat?
If she were my sister, I'd have smacked her one.
Is this your seat, mister?
That's not it.
All these elderly people are standing uncomfortably.
And you're not even really asleep.
Can't you give them your seat?
- It's all right. - Right, ma'am.
This is a regular seat, not one for the elderly, you know.
My ankle hurts, so I want to sit down too.
Is there something wrong with that?
No, it's not wrong.
It's not.
But think of your own grandparents. If you give up your seat,
It will bring you good fortune.
I don't need any good fortune.
And I don't have grandparents at home.
Also, forcing someone to be courteous...
Is a type of harassment.
If you're so desperate for them to have a seat,
You could have thrown yourself or your bag...
To save an empty seat for them.
Right, right. My mistake.
I shouldn't have opened my mouth.
Go on, just sit there comfortably for the rest of the ride.
No wonder your ankle hurts, wearing shoes like that.
This guy is unbelievable.
What I wear is none of your business.
The nerve of some people.
- What's the world coming to? - The nerve of some people.
This world is going to the dogs.
How pitiful. Those poor shoes.
What the? Is he following me?
Darn it.
Oh my!
Oh, dear. Miss.
Miss, are you all right? Try to get up. Oh, dear.
My gosh.
Are you okay?
Why were you following me? It was creepy.
What? Me? When did I do that?
Just because I said something to you on the bus...
- you followed me to get revenge. - Revenge?
If you keep following me, I'm going to scream.
Give me a break.
What, do you think you're the only one who lives here?
I live here too, you know.
What, you want me to show you my ID? Here. Look. See for yourself. Here.
See?
Seriously. What do you take me for?
Oh, dear. They all fell out.
Darn it.
Hey, can I give you a hand with that?
I'm good at this. Here, let me see.
Wow, this is really, really bent out of shape.
All right.
Wait a second.
There.
Wow, that's on there good and solid now.
There you go.
It's on there tight, right? Here.
Are you insane?
It's all right.
It's not like it was some amazing skill or anything.
Do you know how much these shoes cost?
You just banged them all up. Darn it,
They're all scratched and scuffed.
What are you going to do about this?
Pay for them.
I try to do a good deed, and this is the thanks I get?
I fixed them. Pay for the repair...
- or at least thank me. - When did I ask you to fix them?
You grabbed my shoes and completely ruined them.
Besides, if you hadn't been creepily following me in the first place,
I wouldn't have fallen while trying to get away.
I'm so upset.
What is this now?
Hey, I'm the one who should be crying here.
All right, all right. I'll pay for them.
I'll pay for them, and that'll be the end of it, okay?
Don't cry. Just wait a second.
Here, check it.
(Nara Bank)
You could've just transferred the money from your phone.
Do you not know how?
- You've never done it before? - I know how to do it.
Just because I didn't transfer the money,
You're treating me like I'm from the Stone Age or something.
Here. Take this.
Wear them or don't.
I'm fine.
That wretched, rotten girl.
I hope she doesn't get ten steps before her feet start to hurt.
Hmph. I'll just give these to my mom.
(Kids with no one at home to feed them or who are hungry...)
(Kids with no one at home to feed them or who are hungry,)
(eat your fill. It's on the house.)
Oh my, you startled me.
Can I help you with this?
Oh, yes.
(Eat your fill. It's on the house.)
Oh, thank you so much.
Are you a student?
Yes, I guess...
All right, what can I get for you?
One serving each of tteokbokki, sundae,
- and fried snacks to go, please. - Okay, and for the sundae?
And what kind of fried snacks would you like?
Just the sausage and liver for the sundae, please.
For the fried snacks, just give me a mix of whatever.
Well, I have to slice the sundae and heat up the fried snacks,
So have something to eat while you wait. Whatever you want.
As a little thank you for helping me with that paper,
It's on the house.
Thank you.
Goodness, don't be shy. Dig in.
It's the signature dish of our food cart.
Have a taste of the fish cake first.
I'm telling you, it's to die for.
Go on, try it.
Thank you.
So? It's delicious, right?
- Yes. - Grandma's tteokbokki is the best.
- You should stop eating. - Grandma.
- Oh my, Hee Na. You're here. - Hello.
- Yes. - And I see you brought your shadow.
- Yes. - It's my treat.
Wait, what?
It's you, right? It was about a year ago...
Do you know him?
It's nothing...
I'll send the wages I couldn't give you...
Last time to your account. Please give me your account number.
No, it's okay. I wasn't trying to get paid.
Wages? What part-time job?
It's a long story.
Look, Grandma needs to use the restroom for a bit,
So, Hee Na, you watch the cart.
Is that the place where you fell because the floor was slippery?
- That's the one. - I'll go. What if you fall again?
- Oh, I'll be fine. - Come on, let's go together.
Honey, watch the cart for a bit.
Okay.
- Let's go, Grandma. - While I'm gone,
Eat whatever you want while you wait.
- Okay. - All right.
Hey, my baby.
Are you up?
I was going to wake you,
But you were sleeping so beautifully,
So I just left.
Should we meet around seven?
Yes, I'll come pick you up.
Yes, me too.
Okay.
I love you. Right.
What are you looking at?
- Here you go. Enjoy and come again. - Oh, yes.
Are you sure you don't want your wages?
I hope you have a great night, Grandma.
Oh, I told you it's fine, really.
- Oh dear. - Seriously, who is he?
A very stubborn part-timer.
(City Bus Route Map)
(Mu Jin)
I'm sorry.
I really didn't mean to lie to you.
I swear on my father.
You're not sick or in trouble, are you?
I'm worried,
So if you're okay, just send me a period.
(Park Entrance)
Han Gyu Rim?
Who are you?
I'm Chairman Hong Ok Seon's secretary.
Who is Chairman Hong Ok Seon?
She's Kim Mu Jin's mother.
The Chairman would like to see you for a moment.
But I have to get to my part-time job...
I've already informed the restaurant.
Did you go to the late chairman's grave with him today?
Yes, well...
I went to pay my respects at Mu Jin's father's grave.
Let's go.
(Park Entrance)
Thank you.
(Chairman Hong Ok Seon)
Is something wrong with Gyu Rim?
Is she sick?
I mean, she's been late before,
But she's never missed a single day of work.
Gyu Rim isn't home right now.
She went to her part-time job.
Is that right?
(Gyu Rim)
The phone is off, so you will be connected to voicemail.
Call charges will apply after the tone...
Thanks.
- Come in. - Welcome.
Hello.
- It's been a while. - Yes, it certainly has.
I called Hoon Tae to ask him out for a meal,
But he said he wouldn't eat with another woman without his wife.
There you go talking nonsense again, Chairman Hong.
I've been asking her to have a meal with me for years,
And she never comes, and now she just shows up out of the blue.
It's good to see you.
I made spicy braised pork ribs.
You're all right with spicy food, aren't you?
It's my absolute favourite.
I've actually been really stressed out lately,
And I was craving something spicy. Thank you.
After hearing so much about it,
I finally get to taste Seo Hyun's mom's cooking.
Oh, please.
Hey, don't go spreading rumours, all right?
It'll be a pain if people start flocking here.
It's well past mealtime. You must be starving, right?
Come on.
(28 Sadangbon-ro)
Oh, my.
- She's really digging in. - This is delicious.
Seo Hyun's mom, I heard you don't use any housekeepers?
That's right.
When it comes to feeding and clothing my family,
I want to do it with my own two hands.
- But I do hire people to clean. - Hey, you'll get indigestion.
I'm not going to steal it from you, so eat slowly.
Oh my. It doesn't taste as good if I eat it slowly.
Hey, your wife's cooking is no joke.
Right?
Out of everything I've ever eaten, this is the best. Really.
Excuse me.
I'll invest. Why don't you open a restaurant?
Oh, I'm not good enough to open a restaurant.
I'll let you two talk.
- Let me know if you need anything. - Okay.
Please, join us.
I brought this wine, too.
It was hard to get, so please have some with us.
I'm completely charmed by you.
I want to be friends.
She's right. Come have a glass of wine with us.
Sit down. Come on.
All right, then.
Come on, sit down.
What was that?
Mu Jin is seeing someone else?
Then where does that leave our Seo Hyun?
She can't hold a candle to Seo Hyun.
Of all the people to date,
How could he choose someone so beneath him?
He must be out of his mind.
Unbelievable.
Still...
Your son must see something good in her,
Which is why he's dating her, don't you think?
Something good?
Listen.
I had my assistant, Secretary Cha, do a background check on her.
She comes from a dirt-poor family.
She has a single father and a bunch of younger siblings.
And on top of that, she only has a high school diploma.
Who knows what she was doing,
But she couldn't even get into a college that anyone can get into.
And our Seo Hyun lost to a girl like that?
It really hurts my pride.
I mean, does Mu Jin have such bad judgment?
Is he that bad at judging women?
- Honey. - Honestly.
So, how did they meet?
She works at the restaurant where our Mu Jin is in training.
She's a part-timer there.
According to Secretary Cha,
She probably doesn't know who Mu Jin really is, but...
No, no. She knows exactly who he is.
She thinks she's hit the jackpot. She's stuck to him like a leech...
And is just sucking him dry. That little witch.
She must be a gold digger.
Oh, right. A gold digger. Yes. She must be a gold digger.
- Honey. - What?
Oh, why are you acting so unlike yourself?
Because I'm upset. Okay? I mean, our Seo Hyun.
What could she possibly be lacking?
Oh, forget it. A guy like Mu Jin.
- I wouldn't take him by truckload. - Oh, honestly.
Oh, this man. Are you drunk?
Hey, don't worry.
I'll take care of everything.
I mean, how could I accept someone so beneath us...
As my daughter-in-law?
Hey, do you know who I am?
I'm Hong Ok Seon.
The sky could fall, and it would still be impossible.
Oh, I'll go make some soup to help you sober up.
Let's have our children marry.
- Seriously? - What?
Who says we'll be in-laws? I told you I don't want to.
I told you I wouldn't take Mu Jin even if he came by the truckload.
Not with you, Hoon Tae.
I said I'm becoming in-laws with Yoon Hee. Why?
You know, Yoon Hee,
I was completely charmed by you today.
My mother used to say,
When a mother can make such a wonderful...
And comforting meal, the daughter she raises...
Is a bride you should take, sight unseen.
Enough of that.
- Thank you for your kind words. - Hey, it's time for you to go. Go.
My feelings are hurt today.
You're finished eating, right? Go home. Now.
Honey, honestly.
Please, you have to let me have Seo Hyun.
No, it's just because they grew up together.
He just doesn't see her as a woman yet.
Mu Jin will come to his senses. All right?
I said that's enough, Chairman Hong.
All right? I'm the one who's against it.
I have my pride too, you know.
We will absolutely not become in-laws.
My gosh.
- Cheers. - Right, cheers.
Not with you. Cheers. Yoon Hee, cheers.
So what are you going to do about it?
Where's the Chairman?
She had something urgent come up today,
So she had to step out.
The person who asked to meet me today,
Wasn't that the Chairman?
Well...
After rethinking it,
The Chairman decided that there was no longer a need...
Or value in meeting with you directly.
What is this?
It's 100,000 dollars.
Is this how you tell me to break up with Mu Jin?
In such a petty and cruel way?
If it's not enough, we can offer you more.
- Give me 100,000,000 dollars. - One hundred...
Did you say 100,000,000 dollars?
You're asking me to put a price tag on my feelings for Mu Jin, right?
Give me 100,000,000 dollars.
Han Gyu Rim.
I may not be very educated, but I'm good at basic math.
Anything less is out of the question.
Give me 100,000,000 dollars. Then I'll break up with him.
(28 Sadangbon-ro)
(Gyu Rim)
Where are you?
- Are you trying to drive me crazy? - I'm hungry.
I'm starving.
(Damga Charcoal Grill)
Over here.
Gyu Rim.
You're here. Sit down.
You haven't eaten either, right, Mu Jin?
I'll order some more meat.
Want a drink too?
What happened?
Where have you been all this time?
I had to do some thinking.
But I'm done thinking now.
If I'm going to date you,
I have to build up my strength first.
If I want to withstand a typhoon,
I realised that my usual strength won't be nearly enough.
Does that mean you forgive me?
Yes.
I can only imagine how desperate you were.
I understand you now, Mu Jin.
Even if we break up someday,
It won't be now.
Break up? Why would we break up?
That will never happen as long as you don't leave me.
Okay.
I was worried all day that you were going to break up with me.
You didn't answer your phone. You didn't show up for work.
I thought you were sick, so I went to your house,
But Gyu Min said you went to work.
I got so scared that something had really happened to you...
That I was on edge all day.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for making you worry.
Do you know how scared I was?
Mu Jin, come on.
Why are you acting like a child? People are watching.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I'm sorry I worried you.
How long do we have to wait?
I'm telling you, Hyun Soo was with another girl.
If you don't believe me, go and see for yourself.
Hee Na.
I'm at a funeral right now, so it's not a good time to talk.
Is something wrong?
Hey, Park Hyun Soo!
You call this a funeral home?
Hee Na.
It's certainly a hip place.
I thought you said your great-aunt passed away.
Since I'm here, I might as well pay my respects.
Well, Hee Na...
You see...
What happened was...
My great-aunt almost died, but then miraculously...
Hey, Park Hyun Soo.
Jae Hee.
Who are you?
And who are you?
Is this your great-aunt?
What is she talking about?
Hey, Park Hyun Soo. You answer me.
- Who is she? - What?
Are you trying to decide which one of us to dump?
What are you talking about? Look, what happened was...
Hey, forget it.
Instead, I'm dumping you.
Now you don't have to sneak around anymore.
This girl, that girl, every other girl.
Go date them all.
- Jae Hee, wait. Hear me out. - You punk!
Darn it.
Hey, where are you going?
Hey!
Let go.
Hey, happy now that you've made a fool of me and are leaving?
Are you?
You should be grateful that I'm ending it here.
You worthless piece of trash.
Unbelievable.
You little punk. Darn it.
What do you want, you punk?
- Give me 50 dollars. - What?
What do you mean by 50 dollars?
Earlier, in front of the tteokbokki stand,
You stole 50 dollars from the cash box...
And shoved it in your pocket.
What? When did I do that?
When the old woman went to the restroom.
Seriously?
You really stole from her?
Let go.
Let go, darn it.
Are you okay?
You always seem to...
See me at my most embarrassing.
I have a bad memory, so I'll forget it soon.
So don't worry about it.
What is it?
Mom's waiting for you.
That girl...
Did you take her to your father's grave?
Yes.
I thought you were just playing around...
And would break up with her.
Were you serious?
Yes.
Then if I were to tell you to break up,
You wouldn't do it so easily, would you?
That's right.
Even if you want me to, I will never break up with her.
Then what are we to do?
I'll never accept that girl as long as I live.
She's marrying me, not you.
Is that so?
Then choose.
Either give up everything you enjoy thanks to me...
Or dump that girl.
What's it going to be?
Fine.
I'll give it all back. Everything I got from you.
Fine, then.
The stocks, real estate, and cash you have just because you're my son,
And everything down to your last pair of socks.
Hand it all over.
And get out of here with nothing.
Fine.
I'll do that.
Mu Jin.
Mom. Mu Jin is really packing his bags.
He didn't earn a single thing in this house.
Tell him to leave with just the clothes on his back.
Mom.
Kim Mu Jin.
This is just a fleeting feeling.
She's not worth giving up everything you have...
And risking it all.
Please take care of Mom.
Mu Jin.
I've been through this myself.
So?
Don't you have any regrets?
None at all.
If I let Gyu Rim go now,
I know I'll regret it for the rest of my life.
Hey.
Kim Mu Jin.
(I'll Protect My Daughter! Hunger Strike: Day One)
Mom.
What am I going to do?
I'm scared.
I'm so, so scared.
(Mu Jin)
Hello?
Were you asleep?
No, I was just about to fall asleep. What about you?
Are you outside?
I couldn't sleep,
So I came out for a walk.
Gyu Rim.
Yes?
No matter what happens,
Don't give up on me.
Okay.
Good.
That's all I needed to hear.
I love you, Mu Jin.
Gyu Rim, do you realise...
This is the first time you've said you love me?
Really?
Yes.
That's all I need.
For today,
That's all I needed.
I love you too, Han Gyu Rim.
Sleep well.
Watch out.
(Love on the Menu)
How badly is he hurt? It's not life-threatening, is it?
Han Gyu Rim.
What do you even know about Mu Jin? Didn't you notice anything?
Mu Jin...
Gave up everything for you.
- We lost our house. - What are you talking about?
From now on, it's every person for themselves.
Then what about Gyu Min and Gyu Seo?
I told you, we should just dump them at an orphanage.
Shut your mouth, Han Gyu Young.
Fine. You all have a nice life together.
Just give me 100,000 dollars.
For 100,000 dollars to leave Mu Jin,
That seems like a pretty good deal.